Ok. What I'm going to be performing here is called a front squat. Now, the traditional squat usually you see the bar behind the neck.
This is in front of your body.
It's going to be laying on your shoulders.
Cross over your arms to keep the bar steady and to hold there.
Now, the front squat develops your teardrop.
That's what we call it at the gym.
Which, is the front part of your quads that's near the knee cap.
You want to go down with the bar, come up.
Again, just like the squat you want to push from the heels.
Keep your body steady throughout the whole flow.
Do about, depending on the amount of weight you're doing if you're going real heavy do about eight to ten reps.
If going real light, you want to to about ten to fifteen.
Again, the front squat you're going to concentrate a lot on the front part next to the knee cap to help develop those better.
And, that's how you perform the front squat.